And now we will have the reading of the
law
start in Exodus the 20th chapter verses
1-1 17.
Go ahead.
And God spake all these words, saying, I
am the Lord thy God, which hath brought
thee out of the land of Egypt, out of
the house of bondage. Thou shall have no
other gods before me. Thou shall not
make unto thee any graven image, or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above, or that is in the earth beneath,
or that is in the water under the earth.
Thou shall not bow down thyself to them,
nor serve them. I the Lord thy God. God,
I'm a jealous God, feeding the iniquity
of the fathers upon the children, and to
the third and fourth generation of them
that hate me, and showing mercy unto
thousands of them that love me and keep
my commandments. Thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain, for
the Lord will not hold him guiltless
that taketh his name in vain. Remember
the Sabbath day, and keep it holy. Six
days sh thou labor and do all thy work.
But the seventh day is the Sabbath of
the Lord thy God. In it thou shall not
do any work. Thou nor thy son, nor thy
daughter, thy man's servant, nor thy
maid servant, nor thy cattle, nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates. For
in six days the Lord made heaven and
earth, the sea, and all that in them is,
and rested the seventh day, before the
Lord blessed the Sabbath day, and
hollowed it. Honor thy father and thy
mother, that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee. Thou shall not kill. Thou shall
not commit adultery. Thou shall not
steal. Thou shall not bear false witness
against thy neighbor. Thou shall not
coveret thy neighbor's house. Thou shall
not coveret thy neighbor's wife, nor his
man's servant, nor his maid servant, nor
his ax, nor his ass, nor anything that
is thy neighbor. Let's go into
Ecclesiastes the 12th chapter. Read
verses 13 and 14.
Go ahead. Let us hear the conclusion of
the whole matter. Fear God and keep his
commandments.
For this is the whole duty of man. For
God shall bring every work into judgment
with every secret thing whether it be
good or whether it be evil. Let's go to
Revelation chapter 22
14 and 15.
Go ahead.
Blessed are they that do his
commandments,
that they may have right to the tree of
life, and may enter in through the gates
into the city. For without our dogs, and
sorcerers, and whoreongers, and
murderers, and idoltors, and whosoever
loveth and maketh the lie. So, we want
to thank God for the reading of the law.
As we showed in the lesson yesterday,
anybody that say that you don't have to
keep the law or the commandments, they
don't know God. No, it's all that
simple.
And we going to get
right into this lesson, sisters and
brothers, so we can get right into the
food.
[laughter]
This is the day of Pentecost.
And if you find yourself
present
on this day
and you're not in the fire,
you are God.
>> It's all that simple.
You see there are a lot of days that
uh
some my Israelite brothers and also the
Edomite the so-called Jew keep you know
like in dedication like Pum you know and
several others we only keep what's
written in the 23rd chapter of Leviticus
because
Leviticus the 23rd chapter is a road
mapap to salvation
and it's talked about things that's
going to get you salvation. We don't do
nothing just to carry on a ritual.
Like we have some people have some kind
of uh uh uh gathering every new moon
which have no significance.
this
the 23rd chapter of Lev Leviticus have
all the plan that you need to get
salvation. All you got to do is read it
and understand it.
So we're going to start this in
Leviticus the 23rd chapter
and we're going to start at verse one.
Leviticus 23
and verse one.
Okay, go ahead.
And the Lord spake unto Moses, saying,
speaking to the children of Israel, and
saying to them,
>> Go ahead.
>> Concerning the feast of the Lord,
concerning the feast of the Lord, not
the feast of the Jews. These are the
feast of the Lord. Go ahead and read.
>> Which you shall proclaim to be holy
convocations.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Even these are my feasts.
>> Now, he said, which you shall proclaim
be to be holy convocation. Other words,
you're supposed to have a gathering like
this. This is a holy gathering, sisters
and brothers. We're here for one reason
and one reason alone, and that's to
acknowledge our God and his plan,
>> right? Skip down to verse four and read
it.
>> These are the feasts of the Lord.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Even holy convocation.
>> Go ahead.
>> Which you shall proclaim in their
season.
>> And you got to proclaim them in their
season. You can't just proclaim them any
time, sisters and brothers. It's just
like Passover. They call that the last
summer supper. They call it communion.
And they some do it every
first Sunday, some do it every second
Sunday, some do it every Sunday. It's
just like if you kept your birthday
every Sunday, you forgot. You forget
when you was born, right?
>> Right.
>> So the Lord said, "Do us in that season
and in that time." So, we're going to
skip now to verse nine and get to the
feast that [clears throat] at hand.
Verse nine, go ahead.
>> And the Lord spake to Moses, saying,
speaking to the children of Israel, and
saying to them,
>> Uh-huh.
>> when ye come into the land which I give
unto you,
>> go ahead.
>> You shall reap the harvest thereof.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And ye shall bring a sheath of the first
fruits of your harvest into the priests.
Now, when you go in the land, when you
plant your crop, and when you reap your
harvest, you shall bring a sheath of the
first fruit to the priest. We're going
to show you how this chapter is telling
you about spiritual things. Go ahead and
read. He shall wave the sheath before
the Lord.
>> Uhhuh. To be accepted for you. Go ahead.
>> On the tomorrow after the Sabbath, the
priest shall wave it. So no matter when
it came up, if it came up Monday,
Tuesday, or Wednesday, when your crop
when you reap the harvest, you have to
wait until the first day of the week.
That's tomorrow after
the Sabbath day.
>> Yes, sir.
>> That's why we have it on Sunday because
this is tomorrow after the Sabbath day
because yesterday was the Sabbath day.
>> Even the Christian Sabbath day. What you
mean? That's a Hebrew Israelite. Don't
you know the original Christians are
Hebrew Israelite? I get tired of people
running around, well, you know, y'all
Hebrew Israelites and we Christians. No,
you ain't. We He Hebrew Israelites and
we are Christians and you are a false
church
cuz I'm getting tired of it being, you
know, being polite to these people
running around distorting the word of
God. What verse are we? That was the end
of 10. The end of 10. Go ahead. And he
shall wave the sheath before the Lord.
Go ahead.
>> Be accepted for you.
>> On tomorrow after the Sabbath the priest
shall wave it.
>> You're going to wave it. What else do
you do? Go ahead and read.
>> He shall offer that day wave his sheath
a heel lamb without blemish of the first
year for a burnt offering unto the Lord.
So now you have to wave a heam of the
first year without blemish along with
the first fruit. that he lamb is not
there just to uh h make up space.
Sisters and brothers, we're going to run
this thing down. Go ahead and read. And
the meat offering thereof shall be two
temp deals of fine flour mingle with
oil. Go ahead. An offering made by fire
unto the Lord for a sweet savor. Uh-huh.
And the drink offering thereof shall be
a wine. Wait a minute. The Lord telling
you to offer wine, too. Yes, sir.
>> But that's what they said. Smoking and
drinking is a sin. Sisters and brothers,
these people don't have I'm not even
going to go there. [laughter]
Just keep reading.
End of 13. Uh-huh.
And the drink offering there shall be a
wine. The fourth part of behind. Go
ahead. Ye shall eat neither bread nor
parched corn nor green ears until the
selfsame day that ye have brought an
offering unto your God. and it shall be
a statue forever throughout your
generations in all your dwellings. So as
long as you dwelling somewhere, the Lord
is always going to point a place for you
to hold this feast.
>> In the early days, some of the old
Hebrew Israelites, some of us, some of
them that knew who he was that find out,
they said, "We can't keep the feast
because you in your enemy's land." I
said, "The book said all your
dwellings." Yes, sir. Dwell me wherever
you living at. You're supposed to keep
this. Now, give me an idea what this
represents, sisters and brothers.
So when you get your crops and you get
the first fruit, why are you got have
you do you have to wave a sheep before
the Lord and it have to be accepted
before you can eat any of it? No corn,
no nothing. Now, let's go and show you
what this is really representing. Let's
go into St. John the 20th chapter.
St. John the 20th chapter. See, the Lord
don't have nothing in the Bible that
don't point toward his purpose. And his
purpose is to create beings just like
him.
St. John chapter 20. Now, this is after
Jesus had got crucified, sisters and
brothers.
And then the women was going to the
supper
to dress him up. You know, they made
spices and all kind of sweet stuff.
That's what they did to the dead. But
they couldn't do it right away because
they had to rest on the Sabbath day,
>> right? Which was yesterday.
And once the Sabbath day was over with,
then they went to the supplicer so they
could with spices and stuff to dress
Jesus' body. And let's show you what
happened when and what time they went
there and what happened when they got
there. St. John 20 and verse one. 20 and
one. Okay, go ahead. The first day of
the week, cometh Mary Magdalene early.
Uh-huh. When it was yet dark. Wait a
minute. Can't be. Cuz you know that's
right. to have sunrise service every
Easter.
So, how can you have sunrise service if
it's still dark, right?
Maybe somebody don't know what they're
talking about. No, they don't.
Well, anyway, maybe they caught him
rising. Keep reading.
Until the supplicant and seeth a stone
taken away from the supplicant. Go
ahead. Then she runth and cometh to
Simon Peter and to the other disciple
whom Jesus loved and said unto them, uh,
they have taken away the Lord out of the
suppl and we know not where they have
laid him. So when they got to the sea of
the grave, Jesus was gone
and it was still dark.
So next time some of your relative want
to get smart and say, I'm going to
sunrise service Sunday morning. So what
you doing? You're going to watch the r
the sun rise
cuz Jesus wasn't there when the day
broke.
Go ahead and read. Peter therefore went
forth and that other disciple and came
to the supplicer. Go ahead. And then and
they came to the suppler. Skip down to
verse eight. So we won't keep you here
all day. Verse eight. Go ahead and read.
Then went in also that other disciple
which came first to the suppl and he saw
and believed. Go ahead.
For as yet they knew not the scripture
that he must rise again from the dead.
That show you that Israel don't pay no
attention. Jesus kept telling them that
he was going to be killed and he going
to rise on the third day.
>> Them apostles wasn't even listening cuz
they didn't know. And plus again too it
says here they did not know the
scripture.
Everything is here is written in the
scripture sisters and brothers.
That's why I said the testimony of Jesus
is the spirit of prophecy. It's the word
of prophecy. What verse?
>> 10. Go ahead.
>> Then the disciples went away again into
their own home.
>> Then they went away. Go ahead. But Mary
stood without at the supplas weeping.
>> Go ahead.
>> And as she wept, she stooped down and
looked into the supplicer.
>> Go ahead. And seeing two angels in white
sitting, one at the head and the other
at the feet.
>> Go ahead.
>> Where the body of Jesus had lain.
>> Uhhuh. And they say unto her, woman, why
weep was thou? She said unto him,
because they have taken away my Lord,
and I know not where they have laid him.
So that's why she's crying, cuz they
didn't understand that he was supposed
to rise. But go ahead and read. And when
she had thus said, she turned herself
back and saw Jesus standing, and knew
not that it was Jesus.
>> Go ahead. Jesus said unto her, Woman,
why weepest thou?
>> Uh-huh. Who seekest thou?
>> Go ahead. She supposed him to be the
gardener. Said unto him, Sir, if thou
have borne him hence, tell me where thou
has laid him, now I take him away. Go
ahead. Jesus said unto her, Mary, she
turned herself and said it to him,
Raboni. Now, that's when she recognized
who he was. You know Jesus did that in
several times in the book. He would
withhold your eye till you couldn't
recognize him.
>> Right?
>> But when he said Mary, then she
recognized him. She saw him and she
said, "Master, that's the bone eye." And
what did Jesus say? Go ahead. Jesus said
it to her, "Touch me not. Touch me not."
Wait a minute. Why wouldn't this woman
be able to touch Jesus after he rose
from the dead?
Why? Go ahead and read. I am not yet
ascended to my father,
but go to my brethren and say unto them,
I send to my father and your father and
to my God and your God. Now, why
couldn't she touch him? And don't you
know this has happened to be on tomorrow
after the Sabbath day?
>> Yeah.
>> She couldn't touch him because he is the
first fruit. Sisters and brothers.
That's what they was telling in
Leviticus the 28th chapter. When you
reap the harvest, I don't want you to
eat parched corn or nothing until you
offer
first fruit and wave it before God.
Right? because it's telling you
that Jesus
somebody was going to come and die for
your sin and they going to come up out
of that grave and they are going to be
the only one the first that came out of
the grave and live forever sister and
brother.
So she couldn't touch him because he had
to go to heaven first and be accepted
right because he was the first fruit.
But let's go in the first Corinthians
15th chapter
and pursue this to let you know we're
not just keeping a feast just to be
having a ritual.
But we kept a feast and we sure ate
good.
But your first meal you getting it right
now. And your best meal you getting it
right now.
No matter what you eat once this is over
with won't compare to what you are
consuming now. system by
>> because what you're doing right now,
believe it or not, you're eating from
the tree of life.
>> 15 and we're going to start reading at
verse 20. 15 and verse 20. Okay, go
ahead.
But now is Christ risen from the dead
and become the first fruits of them that
slept. And become what? The first fruit.
>> The first fruit of them that slept.
Look,
the prophets raised people from the
dead.
Several of them. But every one of them
died again. When Jesus died on the
cross, people was risen out of the grave
and went into the city and showed
themselves.
But they all died again.
But Jesus is the first one that come out
of the grave and didn't die again.
That's why he's the first fruit. Go
ahead and read. For since by man came
death, by man came also the resurrection
of the dead. Go ahead. For as in Adam
all die, even so in Christ shall all be
made alive. Isn't that something? We the
one that brought death into creation.
Yeah. People always blaming God for this
and getting mad when things happen. Like
I had a brother told one time uh uh my
supervisor one time said something about
his daughter when I was working. You
know, I'm mad at God.
I didn't say nothing because I know he
didn't know better. But what we are
suffering now, death, sickness,
hardship,
was brought on us by us.
Go ahead and read.
For since by man came death, by man came
also the resurrection of the dead.
>> Uhhuh.
>> For as in Adam all die. Go ahead. And so
in Christ shall all be made alive.
>> And ain't nobody else going to be able
to bring you back but him. Cuz this his
name is the only one given where you
might be saved. Go ahead and read. But
every man in his own order. But every
man in his own order, Christ the first
fruits. Christ the first fruits.
Afterwards they that are Christ at his
coming. Afterwards they that are Christ
at his coming. This says a mouthful
because it debunks all them lies going
to be told today in them churches by
people in heaven.
If Christ is the first fruit and you and
nobody else is going to be raised until
he come, then who is in heaven?
That's why I say what they teaching that
the Gentiles gave our ministers and
they've been teaching it every Sunday is
so easy to tear down
because it don't coincide with the book.
So Christ the first fruit and those
that are his at his coming.
So now we know why the Lord told you
when you reap your first fruit, don't
eat parched corn and nothing until you
wave it before the Lord and then you
have to sacrifice a heel of the first
year without blemish. Jesus was the
firstborn and he committed no sin. He
had no blemish. So what we just did
about the first fruit, we just told you
about the spiritual, right?
>> Death and resurrection of Jesus.
and that
we will not have no more like him until
he return. That's a great big message
out of the 23rd chapter of Leviticus,
ain't it?
>> Yes, sir.
>> And that's just a little bit of it.
You going to learn some stuff today.
Let's go back to Leviticus the 23rd
chapter.
That's what you do. You come to Israel
God, you going to learn some stuff.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah. And you're going to go home and
you're going to tell it to your family
and they're going to be mad at you.
Like some people tell, "Well, you know,
I'm going to go and tell my pastor. Show
my pastor some of this." I say, "Uh, he
going to throw you out." Yeah, they
will.
Yeah, they will.
>> Couple weeks later, I look out there.
They sitting there. Why you there?
The pastor threw me out
cuz light and darkness cannot dwell
together.
You ever seen a daytime and dark at the
same time?
>> Can't happen. Leviticus 23, we're going
to start at verse 15. 23 and 15. Okay,
go ahead.
Ye shall count it to you from the mark
after the Sabbath, from the day that ye
brought the sheath of the wave offering.
Go ahead. Seven Sabbath shall be
complete. Now from the day that you wave
the first sheath, you got to do what?
Count seven Sabbath. Go ahead and read.
Evening until tomorrow after the seventh
Sabbath say ye number 50 days. Uhhuh.
And ye shall offer a new meat offering
unto the Lord. Now, even tomorrow after
the Sabbath day, you're going to number
50 days. You're going to offer a new
meat offering unto the Lord, sisters and
brother. Now, this is
the people that's going to be actually
in the first and the second re uh uh uh
resurrection cuz it cannot be offered
until the first day of the week,
tomorrow after the Sabbath.
That's why we got some of the Hebrew
brothers talking about talking about the
uh uh what do they call it? The uh uh
floating moon.
>> No. Yeah. Floating Sabbath.
>> Floating Sabbath day. Like when every
time the moon show up, you start the
first day of the week right there. And
then you start your Sabbath day count
all over. You will never put together 50
days.
>> You will never be able to keep this
feast.
So what's going to happen when you offer
a new meat offering? Go ahead and read.
You shall bring out of your habitation
two way loaves of two ten deals. Uh-huh.
They shall be a fine flour. Go ahead.
They shall be bacon with leaven. Uh-huh.
They are the first fruits unto the Lord.
Now this is the first fruit from among
men that lie. Remember that died.
Remember the other lamb. He lamb had no
blemish.
But when
you bake two loaves of bread with leaven
in it cuz leaven represent sin. sisters
and brothers.
>> Mhm.
>> Everybody in here and sin at one time or
another. That's why you need the blood
of Jesus. Go ahead and read. He shall
offer with the bread seven lambs without
blemish of the first year. Now this time
instead of one seven lambs without
blemish because then they would been
wiped out. Then you understand the sins
have been wiped. Otherwise you wouldn't
have been if God hadn't forgiven your
sin then you wouldn't be among the seven
lamb. But seven is complete.
Go ahead and read. And one young bullock
and two rams. They shall be for a burnt
offering unto the Lord with their meat
offering and their drink offering even
an offering made by father sweet save
unto the Lord. So that wine again that
drink offering
to the Lord sisters and brother. Skip
now to verse 20. Verse 20 and go ahead.
And the priest shall wave them with the
bread of the first fruit of a wave
offering before the Lord. Uh-huh. With
the two lambs. They shall be holy to the
Lord for the priests. Uh-huh. And ye
shall proclaim on the selfsame day that
they may be in holy convocation to you.
You shall do no survile work therein. It
shall be a statue forever in all your
dwellings throughout your generations.
So now this here represent
also the father's kingdom but this is
the talking about us now the first the
one lamb without blemish was talking
about Jesus he was the first fruit
>> but now before and when Jesus come he
going to raise in the first resurrection
he going to raise some people from the
dead
but you don't offer him right away
people don't understand that you got to
go through a thousand ye years of Jesus
ruling this earth before you do that
because then when the Jesus
>> when he come the day hit the Sabbath day
represent the thousand years that he
going to rule this earth and at the end
of the thousand years white throne
judgment everybody's make it that's
going to make it is going to make it
then
Jesus turned the thing over to the
father
what verse was that was in there at 21
Okay. Now, let's go into Acts, the first
chapter.
Acts chapter 1.
And we're going to start reading at
verse one. Acts chapter 1 and verse one.
Okay. Go ahead.
The former treaties have I made, oh
theophilles, of all that Jesus began
both to do and to teach. Go ahead. Until
the day in which he was taken up after
that he through the Holy Ghost had given
commandment unto the apostles whom he
had chosen. Now this is Jes he's talking
about what Jesus did while he here and
while he talk but through then he gave
the commandments through the Holy Ghost.
People think that that's talking about
some spiritual
puff of smoke. That's only talking about
it. angel sisters and brothers, we going
to get to get to some of it, but go
ahead and read.
>> To him also he showed himself alive
after his passion by many infallible
proofs. Go ahead. Then seen of them 40
days and speaking of the things
pertaining to the kingdom of God. So now
after Jesus rose, he hung out on this
earth for another 40 days. That's after
he had gone and been accepted by the
father. Then he came back and he hung
out on this earth for 40 days. sisters
and brothers.
>> So could nobody say he didn't rise? Go
ahead and read. And being assembled
together with them, commanded commanded
them that they should not depart from
Jerusalem and wait for the promise of
the father, which saith he, you have
heard of me.
>> Now that's the that's the Holy Ghost,
but that's the word of God. And they
needed it. Why you why do I know that
they needed it? Because they didn't even
know that he was supposed to die and
rise.
>> Right.
>> We read that, didn't we? Yeah, we do.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> For John truly baptized with water.
>> Uh-huh.
>> For ye shall be baptized with the Holy
Ghost, not many days hence. And that is
the word of God, sisters and brothers,
cuz Jesus told you his word with spirit.
The word that he speak of spirit and
nail life until you baptized with the
word of God. You don't know nothing. You
don't know what's going on.
All you got to do is look at the people
that call themselves Christian and you
and look at the Bible. You say, "These
people don't have a clue what's going
on." Skip down to verse eight and go
ahead.
But ye shall receive power after that
the Holy Ghost has come upon you.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Ye shall be witnesses unto me both in
Jerusalem and in all Judea and in
Samaria.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And into the uttermost parts of the
earth. Now we going to be witness of the
Lord because we are Jehovah's witness,
sisters and brothers. nobody else.
Israel, go ahead and read. And when he
had spoken these things, while they
beheld, he was taken up, and a cloud
received him out of their sight. And he
haven't been back since, sister and
brother. That's when he last at 400 days
he left and went back to heaven. And he
have not been back since. But he told
his apostles, "Stay at Jerusalem. Don't
go nowhere until you receive some power
from on high. That's the Holy Ghost.
That's the word of God. Because
we wasn't ready. No.
But then when did the Lord do it? They
Pentecost. This is the day that the
people said the church took over from
Israel.
How come a How come the Gentiles are not
holding Pentecost all over the world
right now?
You behaving mighty weird for to have
taken something over. Let's go into Acts
the second chapter and we going to break
some things down because we're going to
remove some of the spookery
that the Gentiles and put in the word.
Acts 2 and verse one. Go ahead and read.
And when the day of Pentecost was fully
come, they were all with one accord in
one place. Uh-huh. And suddenly there
came a sound from heaven as of a rushing
mighty wind. Uhhuh.
>> And it filled all the house where they
were sitting.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And they appeared into them clothed in
tongues like as of fire. And it sat upon
each of them. Now all of a sudden when
they was there, they've been keeping
Pentecost all their life.
But this particular Pentecost, something
different happened. While it was all
there in the house in the building, all
of a sudden a rushing wind come there
in the house where they were sitting.
And what happened? And there did what?
They paid into them clothing tongues.
They appeared unto them clothe as a
fire. And it set on either one on each
one of them. Boy, brother Bo, that's got
that I know that's the Holy Ghost.
And what happened? Go ahead and read.
And they were all filled with the Holy
Ghost. There you go. They were all
filled with the Holy Ghost. Go ahead.
And began to speak with other tongues.
And the spirit gave them utterance. And
began to speak with other tongues as the
spirit gave them utterance. Sisters and
brothers,
we're going to show you
who these tongues belong to
by example, sisters and brothers,
because the Lord
uses the angels to deliver his message.
And if the angel didn't bring it, you
don't get it. That's why we said that
Jesus after he got through teaching he
was taken up and he commanded his
service
through his holy spirit.
Every angel is a spirit and the one that
ones that did not follow Satan are holy.
That makes them what?
>> Holy spirit.
>> Yes sir.
>> The word spirit then they they put a
slang word in there holy ghost. But the
ghost means spirit.
Why they call it spirit? Because you
can't see it. But that's not alltogether
true. That God want you to see
something, you're going to see
something. Now, in this particular clay,
you saw tongues, didn't you?
>> Right.
Let's go and look at other instances.
Let's go into Ezekiel the 7th chapter.
Ezekiel chapter 2. We're going to show
you, sisters and brothers,
that there was nothing extraordinary
about this. We just going to remove
I call some of the spookery out of it.
Ezekiel the 2 chapter. Ezekiel chapter
2.
Ezekiel chapter 2.
And we're going to read one verse and
skip
Ezekiel chapter 2
and verse one.
Read it.
And he said unto me, son of man, stand
upon thy feet. And I will speak unto
thee. Now, this is the angel that's
doing the talking here. But I'm going to
show you what he was doing. Skip down to
verse three and read it. And he said
unto me, "Son of man, I send thee unto
the children of Israel to rebellious
nation." Go ahead. That have rebelled
against me. They and their father have
transgressed against me even until this
very day. So I'm singing to Israel a
rebellious nation and we still are
rebellious.
>> Brother Rock brother Rock around talking
about the fringes of our culture. I
forgot one brother told me I don't
forgot who it is told me look rebellion
is our culture
>> even f was added because of our
rebellion right now to verse eight let
me see what he said to Ezekiel go ahead
and read but thou son of man hear what I
say unto thee
>> go ahead
>> be not thou rebellious like that
rebellious house
>> go ahead open thy mouth and eat that I
give thee
>> open thy mouth and eat that I give Uh oh
the law going to give this guy a balona
sandwich.
>> But let's see what he's talking about.
Cuz in the Garden of Eden, he gave you
apples, didn't he?
>> No. No. Oh, he didn't.
>> Oh, I forgot. We holding service on
Sunday. We not the Sunday church. Go
ahead and read. And when I looked,
behold, an hand was sent to me. Uhhuh.
And lo, a roll OF A BOOK WAS THEREIN.
JUST A hand showed up.
Pentecost, a tongue showed up. But here
with Ezekiel, just a hand showed up with
a book in it.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> And he spread it before me.
>> And it was written within and without.
>> Go ahead.
>> And there was written therein
lamentations and warnings and woe.
>> Go ahead.
>> That's it.
>> Now, now he said a book was written
lamentation and woe because it going to
be a lot of lamentation on this world
when the Lord come back.
>> Yeah. And let's see what Ezekiel did
with this book. Let's go into Ezekiel
the 3r chapter
and verse one 3 and one. Go ahead and
read. Moreover, he said unto me, son of
man,
>> eat that thou findest and eat this robe
and go speak into the house of Israel.
How do you eat a book?
>> Read it.
>> By reading it.
>> See people, you know, like when Jesus
breathed on the apostles and they were
full of the Holy Ghost. He breathe. All
he did was teach them.
It's just like we used to see when I was
young. We used to tell sisters, you
talking about you so you sold this and
you saw that, brother. I would breathe
on you and you'll melt like butter. In
other words, I'm going to bring you a
rap that you ain't ready for.
>> Ain't got nothing to do with.
>> Y'all see the point?
I think one musician made a record
called what? The brother brother rap.
That's what we call breathing on you.
So what happened here? He ate this book.
Go ahead and read. So I open my mouth
and he caused me to eat that road.
Uh-huh. And he said it to me. Son of
man, cause thy belly eat and fill thy
bow with this robe that I give thee.
>> Go ahead. Then did I eat it and it was
in my mouth as honey for sweetness. It
was in my mouth cuz it's always good
when it go down but once you try and
take it to your family and they get to
reject it and kick it then it become
bitter in your stomach.
>> Yeah.
So once you get through he done got
through eating this roll. Now what did
the Lord tell him? Go ahead and read.
>> And he saying unto me son of man go get
thee into the house of Israel and speak
with my words unto them.
>> Speak with whose word unto them? Lord,
>> where did he get his word from?
>> Out of the book that he ate.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Y'all understand now?
>> Ain't nothing spookier about this, is
it?
>> You do this in your everyday life. Go
ahead and read.
>> I was in
>> skip now rather to 10 now. Verse 10.
Skip now to verse 10. That's what the
Lord said. Get wisdom and knowledge, but
with all your getting get understanding.
Verse 10. Go ahead and read. Oh, he said
unto me, "Son of man, all my words that
I shall speak unto thee, receive in
thine heart, and hear with thine ears."
>> He told him, "Now, everything I speak to
you, I want you to hear with your ears,
and receive in your mind." Go ahead and
read
>> and go get thee to them of the
captivity, and to the children of thy
people, speak it to them, and tell them,
"Thus say the Lord God, whether they
were here or whether they were forb."
Now, he told you go do it. That's why he
told uh the watchmen, warn the people
from me.
You can't make them do right or wrong,
but you warn them.
>> So whether they listen, take heed or
not, that's on them.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> Go ahead and read. Then the spirit took
me up and I heard behind me a voice of a
great Russian. Wait a minute. You heard
the voice of a great Russian. Go ahead
and read. Saying, "Blessed be the glory
of the Lord from this place." Go ahead.
I heard also the noise of the wings of
the living creature that touch one
another. [clears throat] Excuse me. Now
I heard the noise of a living creature.
That's the wing that's touching one
another. Go ahead and read. And the
noise of the wheels over against them
and the noise of a great rushing. There
was a noise of a great rushing. Wait a
minute. Didn't we read that happened
someplace before?
>> Yes, sir.
>> On the day of Pentecost.
See, but them creatures the wings they
heard right now was them angels
which was the cherub angels that the
Lord always show up with since he put
him there to protect the tree of life
from this man. So now we know them great
big rushing that they had that's the
same sound sisters and brothers
that they have on Pentecost. Ezekiel 3
and verse one uh uh uh let's go f verse
13, right?
>> Yeah. Ezekiel.
>> Now, let's go into Daniel's 5 because
they came to give Ezekiel a message.
And once the message was given, he heard
the wings of him going away like a great
rusher.
It's like a flock of angels coming here.
And you think it's a big wind or what is
that going on? And all of a sudden them
tongue showed up.
>> Ezekiel
only a book showed up. A hand with a
book in it showed up. Now let's go into
Daniel the fifth chapter and we going to
look at Nebuchadnezzar's son that got so
brazen he did something stupid and he
got and he died for it.
>> I tell you, don't play with God. You
mess around with God, you going to die
two times,
man. First time I ain't so worried
about, but the second time you better
worry about it, cuz if you die that
second death, you going to be in the
lake of fire forever.
Daniel's 5, we're going to start reading
at verse one. Daniel's 5 and1. Go ahead
and read. Belshazar the king made a
great feast to a thousand of his lords
and drank wine before the thousands. Go
ahead. Belshazar while he tasted the
wine commanded to bring the gold and
silver vessels which his father
Nebuchadnezzar had taken out of the
temple which was in Jerusalem. Now he
must have got he got pretty drunk man
then cuz the only time if you get drunk
that mean you going to do some stupid
stuff.
>> Yeah you are. So he wanted to bring
these these vessels out of Jerusalem
that Nebuchadnezzar his father had
gotten when he took down Judah. Go ahead
and read. That the king and his princes,
his wives, and his concubines might
drink therein.
>> Oh, he's showing off. Go ahead and read.
Then they brought the golden vessels
that were taken out of the temple of the
house of God, which was at Jerusalem. Go
ahead.
>> And the king and his princes, his wives,
and his concubine drank in them. Look.
Look. He having a big to-do
over the holy vessels that his father
took down got when he took down
Jerusalem. He didn't do it.
Go ahead and read.
They drank wine and praised the gods of
gold and of silver of brass of iron of
wood and of stone. Boy, it was really
something. Praise every god but the one
whose life breath hand they breath is
in. Go ahead and read. In that same hour
came fourth fingers of a man's hand.
Uh-huh. And wrote over against the
candlestick upon the plast of the wall
of the king's palace. Without even doing
that all said poof fingers. It didn't
even set a hand, didn't just the
fingers. That's it. Poof.
And I bet everybody eyes are swallowing.
Went on over to the plaster and wrote on
the wall. What happened to the king now?
Let's see. How drunk was he? What verse
are we? end of the five. Uh-huh. And the
king saw the part of the hand that
wrote. Then the king's continent was
changed AND HIS THOUGHTS TROUBLED HIM.
ALL OF A sudden he wasn't SO TRAPPED NO
MORE. GO AHEAD AND READ. So that the
joints of his loins were loose and his
knees smoke went against another.
>> Have you ever been so scared that your
knees knocked?
>> That's where he was. His knees was
knocking.
>> Yeah.
>> Go ahead. The king cried aloud to bring
in astrologers the called and the suit
said. Uhhuh. And the king spake and said
to the wise men of Babylon, "Whosoever
shall read this writing and show me the
interpretation thereof shall be clothed
with scarlet and have a chain of gold
about his neck and shall be the third
ruler in the kingdom." I mean, he was
desperate, wasn't he? Yeah. Cuz he was
shocked.
You'd be shocked, too. All of us would
be scared. Even though we reading this,
that's four, five fingers, four fingers
in a thumb show up.
It'd be a whole lot of knee knocking up
in here.
>> Starting with me.
So he cried,
but none of the called and none of the
people could answer this. Sisters and
brother, there's another message here.
The Lord gave his word to Israel and
nobody else.
And if we don't pass it on, don't nobody
else get it right.
So none of his wise men, astrologers, or
any people that's supposed to have the
big brains in Babylon can handle it. But
then his mother came up and said, "Look,
you got a man in your kingdom
called Belaza,
but his name is Daniel. He can tell you
where he is." No. No. Right.
>> Yeah.
So that mean when he wrote the writing
on the wall, it wasn't just writing. It
was written in another tongue, an
unknown tongue, wasn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> And what Paul tell you?
If you don't have an interpreter,
don't nobody get edified from it. So
what they did, he listened to his mama
and he brought in Daniel. Skip down to
verse 17. Verse 17 and go ahead. Then
Daniel answered and said before the
king, "Let thy gifts be to thyself."
Uhhuh. "And give thy rewards to
another." See, a true man of God, he
ain't worried about getting money and
getting rich. No. You understand? Y'all
already rich. You got the word of God. I
tell anybody, I'm extremely rich.
>> But I got the word of God.
This will get me immortality and make me
God. So how can you have more riches
than this?
>> Right?
>> Think about it. So give me riches to
other go when I finish that. Yet I will
read the writing to the king and make
known to him the interpretation. I tell
you you can reward anybody. But I tell
you what I'm going to do.
I'm going to read this right. And I'm
going to make known interpretation. You
know why he could do that? Because he is
the priest of God. Daniel is a part of
God's witness.
Skip down to verse 17. Uh f verse 25
rather verse 25 and go ahead. And this
is the writing that was written. Uhhuh.
>> Many many to kill you forest.
>> Go ahead.
>> This is the interpretation of the thing.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Many God have numbered thy kingdom and
finished it.
>> Uhhuh.
>> To kill. Now that's really something.
You're a king now. And somebody tell now
look God the numbers your kingdom
partner and he didn't finished it. Go
ahead to tell I weighed in the balances
and I found one. I put you on the scale
miss and you come up light.
Go ahead.
>> Uhhuh. Thy kingdom is divided and given
to the me and Persians. He didn't say
and will be given to him.
>> He had already given it to him. He
already gave me because he was stupid
enough to drink out of the holy cups,
man.
Go ahead and read. That was the end of
28. And let's see what happened. Skip
down to verse 30 now. Let's see how long
it took him to get around to it. Verse
30. Go ahead. In that night was
Belshazar, the king of the called slain.
Uh-huh. And Darius the Median took the
kingdom being about three score and two
years old. Not that Yeah. Not that
month. That night,
>> not six months,
>> the very night. That's why you really
hacked God off, sister and brother,
>> and to go.
>> You going to get up with your wives and
your concuberines and all that and you
going to show off and drink out of my
holy
>> right
vessels, you got to have a death wish.
I'm going to give you your wish.
Kill him very night, sisters and
brothers. But we saw tongues. We saw a
hand
with a book in it.
>> Now we saw fingers and everyone brought
a message, didn't they?
>> Yes, sir.
This one was brought in an unknown
tongue, but God had Daniels to interpret
it. Now, let's go into Revelation the
10th chapter,
and we're going to see it in another
way.
Revelation chapter 10
cuz you got Pentecostalist churches now
made up out of the day of Pentecost
which they wasn't there because of the
gentile doctrine right and when you go
in there all you hear is babbling
wait a minute what you do oh we speaking
in some unknown tongue yeah even to you
Revelation chapter 10
Revelation chapter 10. You know, brother
D, brother, you shouldn't make fun of uh
uh uh other people religion. I I make
fun of falsehood, right?
Because that's what it is. People get
something real serious.
Try to give them respect of somebody
that know something. You ain't getting
it from me.
10 and one. Go ahead and read. And I saw
another mighty angel come down from
heaven clothed with the cloud. Uhhuh.
And a rainbow was upon his head. Go
ahead. And his face was as it were the
sun, and his feet as pillars of fire.
>> Now, this is an old angel. He saw him,
didn't he? Go ahead and read. And he had
in his hand a little book open.
>> Uh-huh. And he set his right foot upon
the sea, his left foot on the earth. Now
they saw the whole angel this time.
Not his fingers, not his hand with a
book in it, not his tongue. They saw the
whole angel. And what did he have in his
hand? A book. A book. Skip down to verse
eight. Let's see what we're going to do
with this book. Verse eight. Go ahead.
And the voice which I heard from heaven
spake unto me again, and said, "Go and
take the little book which is open in
the hand of the angel which standeth
upon the sea." Go ahead.
>> Upon the earth. And I went unto the
angel and said unto him, "Give me the
little book." And he said unto me, "Take
it and eat it up." Wait a minute. Ain't
that what they That's what Ezekiel was
told.
>> Yeah.
>> Take the book and eat it up. But this is
the whole angel he's looking at now. Go
ahead and read. And it shall make thy
belly bitter. Uh-huh. But it shall be in
thy mouth sweet as honey. It's always
like that. When you get the truth and
you know, boy, it's sweet. You can't
wait to get your old family and tell
them. Then once you get there, then that
sword that Jesus spoke about drops in
the middle of it. Cuz he said, "I come
not to bring peace, but a sword." I'm
going to set family members against
family members.
>> Because you dealing with tradition and
they dealing with tradition. When you
bring this truth, it's going to be war.
>> Yeah.
>> Your first battle is in your to with the
people that you're closest to. Go ahead
and read what verse
>> 10. Go ahead. And I took the little book
out of the angel's hand and ate it up
and it was in my mouth sweet as honey.
Uhhuh. And as soon as I had eaten it, my
belly was billing. Woe is that. Go ahead
and read. Then after he had ate eaten
the book, then what did the angel tell
him? Go ahead and read. And he said unto
me, "Thou must prophesy again before
many peoplesh and nations and tongues
and kings."
And he's doing it right now. And we
reading this book that John wrote. Yeah.
>> But before he wrote it,
he got it from the angel. And the Lord
used the angel to use the book to let
you know
that this ain't something that popped in
your head. All of a sudden, preacher be
preacher. The Holy Ghost just spoke to
me.
>> How come I didn't hear him?
>> Right.
>> Everybody in that room with Bel the
Shaza
saw them finger. Poof. I mean everybody.
He wasn't the only one that saw it. No,
he wasn't.
So now
fire tongue, mouth of angel,
hand with the book in it, hand of an
angel,
four fingers and an angel. Then the
whole angel showed up because that is
the way the Lord operate. Then he said
when Jesus was taken up, he commanded
his apostles by his holy ghost.
>> Now let's go into Acts the 7th chapter.
Acts chapter 7
because they done made this thing so
mysterious until can't nobody understand
it. God is not the author of confusion.
Satan is.
Now, this is what got a brother stone to
death. But we ain't dealing with that
today. Stephan, but Stephan got on these
people cuz he said, "You are just like
your fathers."
>> Acts 7, we going to start reading at
verse 51. Acts 7 and 51. And I'm going
to tell you something. It's the word of
God, too. Got a lot of people killed and
a lot of other people going to die for
it during the great tribulation.
>> But when you know that truth, you stand
up to him and you do your worst,
partner.
cuz you know that you going to be raised
and you going to judge them
and once you get through judging them
you going to put me get put a death on
them that they ain't going to really be
dead and they can't get out of that's
called the lake of fire
Daniel 7 and 51 Daniel 7 and 51
okay
>> uh uh uh
>> Acts
>> Acts I'm sorry Acts 7:51 where y'all got
my notes
Okay, go ahead. Ye stiff neck and
uncircumcised and hard and ears. You do
always resist the Holy Ghost. Go ahead.
As your fathers did. Now he come you
stiff neck and uncircumcised in the
heart. That's the mind
and uh uh uh in your ears. You know what
it mean circumcised? Doesn't mean that
you ain't listening to nothing, right?
A person that refused to get circumcised
physically, he have not been circumcised
spiritually.
>> Right?
>> But the word the first circumcision you
get
is the circumcision of your mind,
sisters and brother.
>> Now they trying to say nowaday people
that's all you got to have. But no, he
said you're just like your fathers. Just
like your fathers, you resist the Holy
Ghost as they did. So do you. Go ahead
and read. So do you. Which of the
prophets have not your fathers
persecuted? Uhhuh. They have slain them
which show which show before of the
coming of the just one of whom ye have
been now the betrayers and murderers.
Now we kill our prophets and we kill
Jesus. Pilot was trying everything he
could to let Jesus off the hook. We tell
him we we tell them well we going to
have to appeal to Caesar because
Caesar's king. Now you trying to save
this guy to say he's a king
and just like Gentiles are when they
feel like they are in jeopardy they will
capitulate.
But we put the people up to uh uh
crucifying Jesus. Now he said which read
that again and we going to read right
right uh uh into the 53rd verse. Which
of the prophets have not your fathers
persecuted? And they have slain them
which show before of the coming of the
just one. Of whom ye have been now the
betrayers and murderers. Go ahead.
>> Who have received the law? By the
disposition of angels.
>> Who?
>> Who have received the law? By what?
>> The disposition of angels.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And have not kept it.
>> So how did we receive the law of God in
this word?
>> As angels.
>> Angels.
That was that bunning bush was an angel
that Moses went and got the message from
the Lord do it. I think he get it with
dramatic since we such a hardheaded
people and we need miracles.
Them angels I don't know whether the
Lord tell them to be dramatic or they do
it on their own. But either way it go
when you see a bush burning it that
don't burn up. That's got your
attention.
Hand shows up with a book in it that got
your attention. finger showed up. That's
got your attention. Fiery tongues, a
mouth show up sitting on you. How is it
you're not going to pay attention to
that? But no matter how they came to
you, sisters and brothers, those are
angels.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
And the spirit that you get filled with,
sisters and brothers, is the word of
God. You can read that on your own in
St. John 6 and 6 uh uh chapter 6 and
verse 63. He's the word that I speak.
They are spirit and they are life
sisters and brothers.
So the angel is the one that bring us
the word
and he bring us the word and the
language that we can speak
>> right
>> and if he bring it in another language
that you can't that we don't speak he
will have an interpreter that
everything we get we got the Lord sent
it by way of an angel
and he going to in it in a way that we
can understand it. Let's go into Isaiah
the 28th chapter.
Isaiah chapter 28.
And the Lord tell you things because he
know he know your condition. What's
going to happen to you? Israel because
we rebel. So he knew he was going to
scatter us. And he did scatter us.
And look what he said. Isaiah 28 and
we're going to start reading at verse 9.
Isaiah 28 and verse 9.
Okay, read it. Whom shall he teach
knowledge?
>> Uhhuh.
>> And whom shall he make to understand
doctrine?
>> Look, look, he said, whom shall he teach
knowledge? And whom shall he cause to
understand doctrine? That's his word,
sisters and brothers.
>> Yeah.
>> Cuz his word is the only thing that
bring knowledge. Go ahead and read.
>> Them that are wean from the milk,
>> Uhhuh.
>> and drawn from the breast. And that milk
he's talking about is the sweet milk of
the word of God. I think that's in uh uh
first Timothy the 2 chapter, something
like that. But anyway,
>> first Peter,
>> huh? First Timothy,
>> first Peter.
>> First Peter, rather the second chapter.
>> Mhm.
>> Say, you know, you got to be weaned from
the sweet milk of the word.
So whom shall we teach knowledge?
And whom
shall the word of God be revealed? What
verse? 10. Go ahead. For precept must be
upon precept.
Precept upon precept. Line upon line.
Line upon line. This how it's got to
come, sisters and brothers. Precept upon
precept. I can't come up and just start
quoting a book and I have to tell you
today we going to teach you about born
again.
And we have to search it out line upon
line. Line up on line. Go ahead and
read.
>> Here a little and there a little.
>> Here a little. Isn't this what we're
doing today?
>> Mhm.
>> Is it the way we do it every time you
come here?
>> Yeah.
>> He a little and there a little. Go ahead
and read.
>> But with stammering lips
>> Uhhuh.
>> and another tongue will he speak to this
people. Now with stammering lip and
another tongue will he speak to this
people. What people he talking about?
Israel.
I don't speak Hebrew.
>> So he's speaking to me in the English
language.
>> Yes sir.
>> Israel scattered all over the country,
all over the world speak whatever
language that of the nation that they
are in and God send them a message in
that language.
Here a little and there a little. Line
upon line, precept upon precept. With
stammering lips and another tongue will
I speak to this people. You know what
that tell me?
That we going to get scattered and we
ain't going to have nobody that's among
Israel that really no Hebrew no more.
>> Yes, sir.
>> He didn't say with stammering lips in
Hebrew and another tongue.
>> No, he didn't. So when somebody come to
you with some so-called Hebrew name, you
just look at them and walk away.
Brother come, well, you know, uh, give
me some Hebrew name or something. I
said, you know, can you tell me in
Hebrew how to walk, walk to the corner,
catch a bus, catch it to the train, L
train, and catch the L and go to the
airport
and catch the plane. Could you tell me
how to do all that in Hebrew?
Then all he can do is look,
>> right?
>> What verse are we?
>> That was the end of 11.
>> Go ahead.
>> To whom he said,
"This is the rest where ye may cause the
weary to rest."
>> Uhhuh.
>> And this is the refreshing yet they
would not hear.
>> Still they wouldn't hear.
They wouldn't hear. No
>> sisters and brothers
because what is the rest that he going
it's worried he tell you look I put you
in captivity
but I'm going to get you out.
Sure you died every day but I'm going to
give immortality back to you. Do this
thing right and you going to be God. Was
that the end of that? That was the end
of that. What was that? Verse 12. Verse
12. Now let's go and Paul told the same
thing but just telling it another way.
This is in tongues chapter where
everybody go. People don't even go to
this tongue chapter. Let's go to the day
of Pentecost.
I remember you know when me and brother
Marsha when we was in business together.
>> Yeah.
>> We had a heating and cooling uh uh uh
company on uh where I'm getting old
Stony Island. So a young guy coming
there and he wanted to he wanted to look
for a job. So we had a furnace up there.
I took him up to the furnace and say,
"Okay, point at the gas bar. What is
that?"
Huh? [laughter]
The thermicouple. What is that? Huh?
The limit control with you. Huh? And you
want a job? You got to go to school,
buddy. You don't know that.
What religious are you? I'm Pentecostal.
Oh, so you keep the day of Pentecost.
What's that?
He was dumb about his religion as he was
about the furnace.
But the whole thing is Paul made it
clear again. 1 Corinthians the 14th
chapter.
See, people hate knowledge
and that is what's going to save you.
How can you escape something and you
don't know how? That's what knowledge
is, know how
1 Corinthians chapter 14
and we're going to start at verse one. 1
Corinthians chapter 14 and verse one.
Okay, read.
Follow after charity and desire
spiritual gifts. Go ahead. And you
should go ahead. But rather you may
prophesy. But rather you prophesy. Go
ahead. Why? What? Why? As opposed to
what? Go ahead and read. For he that
speaketh in an unknown tongue speaketh
not unto men, but unto God. Go ahead.
For no man understandeth him. How be it?
In the spirit he speaketh mysteries. And
that's what it is. If I don't teach you
how to get salvation by way of this book
in a language that you understand, how
can you know how to get it? Go ahead and
read. But he that prophesied speaking to
men to edification and exhortation and
comfort. Now when you speak plainly,
then you are edifying somebody. Skip
down to verse five. Verse five and go
ahead.
>> And I would that ye all speak with
tongues.
>> Uh-huh.
>> But rather that ye prophesy, for greater
is he that prophesize than he that
speaketh with tongues.
>> Uh-huh. Except he interpret that the
church may receive edifying.
>> Didn't Daniel's edifying neverh
Belshazzer with that?
>> He interpreted told partner, you've been
weighed in the balance of your your
kingdom is given to somebody else. Now
skip down to verse 18 and go ahead.
I thank my God I speak with tongues more
than y'all.
>> Uhhuh. Yet in the church, I had rather
speak five words with my understanding,
that by my voice I might teach others
also, than 10,000 words in an unknown
tongue. Wait a minute now. Pretty
constant people don't they don't read
this. Now go ahead and read. Brethren,
be not children in understanding. How be
it in malice be ye children.
>> Uh-huh.
>> But in understanding be men. You better
be man cuz if you ain't a man in
understanding, you will never be God. Go
ahead and read.
>> And the Lord is written
>> with men of other tongues and other lips
will I speak to this people.
>> Now in in uh uh Isaiah 28, he said with
stam lip and another tongue will I speak
to this people. But it said here with
men with stammering lips in another
tongue. In other words, whatever you
know some man got to teach it to you.
>> Go ahead and read. And yet for all that
will they not hear me, sayeth the Lord.
Go ahead. Wherefore tongues are for a
sign. Uhhuh. Not to them that believe,
but to them that believe not,
but prophesying serveth not for them
that believe not, but for them which
believe. So I want you to put that under
your belt next time somebody Pentecost
come you. If you don't speak in tongues,
you ain't got the Holy Ghost. Hit them
with that.
>> That's for nonbeliever.
>> Yeah. But it's in the law. It told you
that with men of other tongue will I
speak of this people. Why? Because all
of us are in nation and they have they
their own language and that's the only
language you have. If you in if you was
find yourself being a a a captive a
slave in Mexico. Yeah. Mexico has slave.
You speak Spanish.
Look at the Haitians speak French. You
know why? Because the French was their
slave owners.
English. The English was our slave
owners. In other words, whatever the
language that our slave owners spoke, we
speak.
in the law. So let us go back to Acts
the second chapter back to the day of
Pentecost
cuz the word being speak is spoken is
nothing if you don't have an interpreter
sisters and brother if you going to
speak in some unknown tongue.
Acts two and five. Acts chapter 2 and
we're going to start reading at verse
five. Okay, go ahead.
And there were dwelling at Jerusalem
Jews, devout men out of every nation
under heaven. Now, I mean that all the
ones that knew who they were, they came
to Jerusalem to keep this particular
day. Go ahead and read. And now when
this was noise abroad, the multitude
came together and were confounded
because that every man heard them
speaking his own language. Wait a
minute. That's why they was confounded.
Everybody went in there. I speak French.
You speak English. You speak Spanish.
You teach German. But everybody heard
them speaking their own language. Go
ahead and read. And they were all amazed
and marvel. Uhhuh. Saying one to other,
"Behold, are not all these which speak
Galileans?" Go ahead. And how here we
every man in our own tongue where we
were born. Uhhuh. Say in our own tongue
which is language where we were born.
These guys are Galileans, right? How is
it our him in Russia?
Go ahead and read. Parththeians and Mes
and Elummites and dwellers in
Mesopotamia and in Judea and Capidosia
and Pontis in Asia and Persia and
Panilia and Egypt and in parts of Libya
about Sirene and strangers of Rome, Jews
and Proelites. Go ahead. Creeks and
Arabians. Uh we do hear them speak in
our own tongues the wonderful works of
God. Didn't the Lord said with men of
other tongue would I speak to his
people?
So Peter was probably speaking Hebrew at
that time or whatever the language, but
you had them fiery tongues to do what?
>> Interpret.
>> Yes, sir.
>> They don't God didn't only send the
message. He sent the interpreters with
them. That's why when they heard that
big Russian come in, that wasn't nothing
but a flock of angels, sisters and
brothers. Right.
>> You see it all the time at the United
Nations when they have a meeting and all
of them have the interpreters there.
>> Yes, sir.
That's what happened on the day of
Pentecost, sisters and brothers.
But everybody there was an Israelite.
Everybody.
That's why I said Jews out of every
nation under the sun.
>> There was not one non-Israelite there.
So, how is it that the church took over
on Pentecost?
>> But why was why was all these people
here? Let's go to Deuteronomy 16 and
find out Deuteronomy chapter 16.
It was here for the same reason that we
are here.
>> Yes, sir.
>> And we're going to read it.
>> Deuteronomy 16. And we're going to read
start reading at 16.
16 and 16.
Okay. Read it. Three times in a year
shall all thy males appear before the
Lord thy God in the place which he shall
choose. Uh-huh. In the feast of unleven
bread, and in the feast of weeks, and in
the feast of tabernacles. Now, that's
the one we hear. Right. Right. Unleaven
bread. Feast of weeks and the feast of
tabernacle. Feast feast of weeks rather
is Pentecost. And then the feast of
tabernacle. Go ahead.
>> And they shall not appear before the
Lord empty.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Every man shall give as he is able
according to the blessing of the Lord
thy God which he hath given thee.
>> See this that you supposed to give on
these high days is different from your
yearly tithe, sisters and brothers.
>> Right.
>> We just haven't been teaching it because
ain't nobody money hungry up in here.
But you supposed to give something, too.
Yeah, you are. But I was asked the
question even yesterday. Well, what
about the women?
Skip back up to verse 10.
Verse 10 and read it. And thou shalt
keep the feast of weeks unto the Lord
thy God with the tribute of a free will
offering of thine hand. Uh-huh. Which
thou shalt give unto the Lord thy God,
according as the Lord thy God have
blessed thee. Go ahead. And thou shalt
rejoice before the Lord thy God, thou
and thy son, and thy daughter, and thy
maid servant, and thy maid man's
servant. Hold on, let me read that
again. and thy daughter, and thy man's
servant, and thy maid servant, and the
Levite that is within thy gates, and the
stranger, and the fatherless, and the
widow that are among you, in the place
which the Lord thy God have chosen to
place his name there. So that let you
know that everybody is supposed to come,
male or female. I just want to throw
that in, sisters and brothers, because
the question come up yesterday. Now
let's go back to Acts the 2 chapter. So
that's why all of these guys Israelites
was from all over the world,
>> right?
>> Because the Lord commanded that you come
before me three times a year.
And like Jack said, don't be empty.
[laughter]
Acts two
and 12.
Acts 2 and we're going to start reading
at verse 12.
2 and 12. Okay, go ahead. And they were
all amazed and were in doubt, saying one
to another, "What mean this?" Others
mocking said, "These men are full of new
wine."
But Peter standing up with the 11 lifted
up his voice and said unto them, "Ye men
of Judea and all ye that dwell at
Jerusalem, be this known unto you and
hearken to my words." Now you know
Peter, some of them said, "Boy, they got
Peter them so drunk they speaking all
these language at one time. You got to
be pretty drunk with that, don't you?"
>> Yeah.
>> But no, Peter said, "This is prophecy.
Go ahead and read."
>> Cuz these are not drunken as you
suppose. Sin is but the third hour of
the day.
>> Uh-huh. But this is that which was
spoken by the prophet Joel. And it came
to pass in the last days, said God, I
will pour out my spirit upon all flesh,
and your sons and your daughters shall
prophesy.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Your young men shall see vision, and
your old men shall dream dreams.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And on my servants, and on my
handmaidaidens, I will pour out my in
those days of my spirit, and they shall
prophesy. Now they let you know that
sister, you can't walk up behind this
roster, but you ain't learning this word
for nothing. You around somebody and
they talking the Bible, you sitting down
and they doing it wrong. Correct them.
Yes, sir.
Have your little old Bible in your
purse.
Whip it out on them
and correct them because the Lord said
you going to prophesy too, didn't you?
>> Yeah.
>> That was a verse. That's was that that's
verse 11 18.
>> 18. Go ahead and read.
>> And I will show wonders in heaven above
and signs in earth beneath.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Blood and fire and vapor smoke. Go
ahead.
>> The sun shall be turned into darkness
and the moon into blood before that
great and notable day of the Lord come.
>> Wait a minute. He took this all all the
way down to the end. Sister brother.
>> He said Joel spoke of this, didn't he?
>> Yeah, he did. Let's go into Joel the
second chapter.
Joel in Hebrew, Joel [laughter]
in Irish
and we're going to start in verse 28.
Joel 2
and 28.
Joel 2 and 28.
Okay,
go ahead. And it shall come to pass
after it, I will pour out my spirit upon
all flesh, and your sons and your
daughters shall prophesy.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Your old men shall dream dreams.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Your young men shall see vision.
>> Pretty clear, ain't it? Go ahead.
>> And also upon the servants, and upon the
handmaids, in those days I pour out my
spirit.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And I will show wonders in the heavens
and in the earth, blood and fire,
pillars of smoke. Go ahead. The sun
shall be turned into darkness and the
moon into blood before the great and
terrible day of the Lord come. Now you
know people always tell it's going to be
a glorious day when Christ come. But
every time we speak of it it's a great
and terrible day ain't it?
>> Yes sir.
>> Let me show you this is talk what this
talking about. Let's go into Revelation
the 6th chapter. Revelation chapter 6.
Oh, I'll be so glad when the Lord come.
Pass the pork chop.
You ain't going to be so glad when the
Lord come.
>> No, you ain't.
>> Cuz I can show you what the Lord said to
people about people that's going to be
eating pig,
man. What's wrong with P?
I said ain't nothing wrong with pig.
Eat it is wrong when the Lord said don't
do it right.
>> That's what make it wrong.
>> Yes sir.
Joel of Revelation rather 6 and 12.
Okay. Go ahead.
And I beheld when he had opened the
sixth seal and lo there was a great
earthquake and the sun became black as
sackloth of hair. Go ahead. And the moon
reclaim his blood.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the stars of heaven fell into the
earth, even as a fig tree car untimely
figs, which she is shaken of a mighty
wind.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the heavens departed as a scroll
when it is rolled together. And every
mountain and island were moved out of
their place.
>> Uhhuh. and the kings of the earth and
the great men and the rich men and the
chief CAPTAINS AND THE MIGHTY MEN and
every barman and every free men hid
themselves in the dens and in the rocks
and in the mountains and said to the
mountains and rocks fall on us and hide
us from the face of him that siteth on
the throne and from the wrath of the
lamb. Have you ever when you come from
your church, did you ever they ever talk
about the wrath of the lamb now? Yes,
>> sir.
They said, "Follow us." Go ahead and
read. For the great day of his wrath is
come, and who shall be able to stand?
>> Look, sisters and brothers, people
talking about when the Lord come, he can
come any day. He can't come any day. The
Lord got this thing plotted out.
>> Yeah, he do.
>> But when he come, you don't want to be
here if your mind ain't right. Let's go
into Matthew the 24th chapter.
>> Isaiah. Uh, I'm sorry. Isaiah the 34th
chapter. Yes, sir.
>> Isaiah chapter 34.
I'm going to speed it up so y'all can
get at that fool.
>> Yeah.
>> Before I get mobbed. [laughter]
Isaiah 34 and we're going to start
reading at verse one.
Isaiah 34
and verse one. Okay. Go ahead. Come then
ye nations to hear and ye people. Let
the earth hear and all that is therein
the world and all things that come forth
of it.
>> Go ahead.
>> For the indignation of the Lord is upon
all nations
>> and his fury upon all their armies. He
have utterly destroyed them. He have
delivered them to the slaughter.
>> That's why they going to be calling for
the rocks to fall on. Go ahead and read.
Their slain out shall shall be cast out
and their stink shall come up out of
their carcasses and the mountain shall
be melted with their blood.
>> He going to kill so many until he got to
bring in carnivorous birds and animals
to eat the bodies. Go ahead and read.
>> And all the hosts of heaven shall be
dissolved and the heaven shall be rolled
TOGETHER AS A SCROLL.
>> How many times that's going to happen?
>> One time. Go ahead.
>> And all the host shall fall down as a
leaf fallth off from the vine and as a
falling fig from the fig tree. Go ahead.
For my sword shall be bathed in heaven.
BEHOLD, IT SHALL COME DOWN UPON ADUMIA
and upon the people of my curse to judge
me. Do you know who I are?
>> The ones that the world called you. The
Lord got a special thing for them. Mhm.
Go ahead and read. The sword of the Lord
is filled with blood. It is made fat
with fatness and with the blood of lambs
and goats and with the fat of the
kidneys of rams. For the Lord ever
sacrificing bulls ra AND A GREAT
SLAUGHTER in the land of Adumia.
>> Oh boy, I hate to be them people. The
Lord got some special punishment for
them.
Why is that? Read verse eight. Verse
eight. Go ahead.
>> For is the day of the Lord's vengeance
and the year recap for the controversy
of Zion.
>> It's the day of the Lord's vengeance and
the repayment for the controversy of
Zion. In other words, I'm going to let
you know who Jerusalem belong.
>> Yes, sir.
>> When he start killing Esau,
which I do.
>> Boy, I almost feel sorry for him. Yeah.
Let's go into Matthew the 24th chapter.
Matthew chapter 24.
I ain't going to feel too sorry cuz I
might get in the Lord's crosshairs.
Matthews 24:1. Go ahead. And Jesus went
out and departed from the temple, and
his disciples came to him, for to show
him the buildings of the temple.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And Jesus said unto them, see not all
these things. Verily, I say unto you,
there should not be left here one stone
upon another that should not be thrown
down.
>> And that happened in 70 AD. Sisters and
brothers, we go ahead and read. And as
he sat upon the mount of olives, the
disciples came unto him privately,
saying, Tell us, when shall these be,
and what shall be the sign of thy coming
and of the end of the world?
>> Go ahead.
>> Jesus answered and said unto them, take
heed that no man deceive you.
>> Pay attention now. He said, "Take heed
that no man deceive you." Go ahead and
read.
>> For many shall come in my name, saying,
I am Christ.
>> For many shall come in my name, saying
that I am Christ. Go ahead.
>> And shall deceive many.
And ain't nobody paid no attention to
No, they haven't.
The biggest deceivers are the one that
come in the name of Jesus. Sister,
brother,
>> what verse was that?
>> In the five.
>> Go ahead.
>> And you shall hear wars and rumors of
wars. See that you be not troubled, for
all these things must come to pass, but
the end is not yet. Haven't we been
doing that? Even with this little thing
that Trump got on with Iran, that don't
b don't bother me. That's a part of
Jesus' prophecy.
>> Yeah.
>> Skip now to verse
14. Now, this is when it gets serious.
Verse 14. Go ahead and read.
>> And this gospel of the kingdom shall be
preached in all the world for witness
unto all nations, and then shall the end
come. I'm trying to bring it cuz I I
ain't going to lie to you. The Lord has
blessed the Israel of God. We are
preaching this gospel to all the
nations.
And we have proof by emails and phone
calls and everything else. We're doing
it. And I want to make it come to an end
cuz I'm tired.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Keep reading. When you therefore shall
see the abomination of desolation spoken
of by Daniel the prophet stand in the
holy place, who so readeth, let him
understand. How many knew about the
abomination of desolation before they
came here? Give me a show of hand.
What
I saw too,
that's really sad, man.
When you see him, who shall read it, let
him understand. What verse was that in
15?
>> Go ahead. Then let them which be Judea
flee to the mountains. Now you got
people, our people going back to
Israel. We going back to the promised
land.
If you are, you making one of the
biggest mistakes of your life. Yeah, you
are.
Why? Skip down to verse 21 and go ahead.
But there shall be great tribulation
such as was not since the beginning of
the world to this time.
>> Go ahead.
>> No, nor ever shall be.
>> Go ahead. And except those days shall be
shortened, that shall no flesh be saved.
But for the elect's sake, those days
shall be shortened. Now sisters and
brothers, they didn't have no weapon at
that time that could kill everything.
But everybody got a weapon now that can
kill everything.
>> The nuclear weapon. Go ahead and read
what verse 23. Go ahead. For if any man
shall say unto you, lo, here is Christ
or there leave it not. And that's what's
going to happen when they build that
temple in Jerusalem. That's the only
place the Palong is going to be
installed in that temple. And that is
the abomination.
And they going to be saying Christ is
back. He said don't believe it. Go
ahead. What verse is that in 23? Finish
it. But there shall arise false Christ
and false prophets. Go ahead.
>> And shall show great signs and wonders
in it SO MUCH THAT IF IT WERE POSSIBLE,
they shall deceive the very elect. They
gonna do that. The books say ain't gonna
cause fire to come down from heaven.
They gonna make a statue. I ain't
talking about no computer. A statue. And
this man going to make that statue walk
and talk.
>> Yes, sir.
>> And if you didn't know that this was
going to happen, you would swap that
this is Christ.
>> Yeah.
>> What verse is that?
>> That was in 24. Let's skip now to verse
27 cuz the Lord letting you know this is
the way I'm coming. Verse 27. Go ahead.
>> For as the lightning cometh out of the
east,
>> Uhhuh.
>> and shineth even into the west.
>> Go ahead. So also the coming of the son
of man shall be. Now see, we know that
being that we know that I don't care how
many statues he may walk or how much
fire he called to come down from heaven.
We know it. You know why? Because we
have the knowledge. And the knowledge
makes us the very elect.
>> Can't fool us. Yes, sir.
>> Why everybody else is flabbergasted and
take back? Whoa. You know what we
saying? Ro, it's about time
because you the very late, right?
And we know what time is going to come.
Just like we see the light and come from
heaven, we going to see him coming in
and the books of every eye going to see
him.
>> But they don't read that because they
keep them out of revelation. Yeah, it
will
>> skip down to verse 29 and go ahead.
>> Immediately after the tribulation of
those days.
>> That mean we got to go through them
tribulation immediately after the
tribulation of those days. Go ahead and
read.
>> Shall the sun be darkened.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And the moon shall not give her light.
>> There it is again. We've been reading
this all afternoon, haven't we?
>> Yeah, we have.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> And the stars shall fall from heaven.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the powers of the heaven shall be
shaken.
>> Go ahead.
>> And then shall appear the sign of the
son of man in heaven. And then shall all
the tribes of the earth mourn,
>> and they shall see the son of man coming
in the clouds of heaven WITH POWER AND
GREAT GLORY. NOW,
everybody's going to see him. Who can
miss when the sun go black and the moon
go red and the stars fall and the HEAVEN
ROLL BACK? HOW YOU GOING TO MISS THAT?
Can't they make the coming of the Lord a
secret?
They don't understand when it say two
women grinding at a meal, one taken and
another left. Two men sleeping in a bed,
one taken, another left. Because they're
going to be the one, the one that's
taken going to be the one that's in the
first resurrection,
>> right?
>> That know the truth.
>> The one that's going to be left is the
one that don't. Yes, sir.
And they going to have to be ruled over
by the one that is taken. Yes, sir.
Let's read a little more something else
to get out of this. Go ahead and read.
>> That was the end of uh 31.
>> That was the end of 31. You sure?
>> Was it?
>> Read it anyway.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yeah, that one end. Let me go back to
30.
>> Verse 31.
>> I got I got caught up. You can't be
getting caught up.
>> Yeah, I know.
It's been a long time.
Verse 31. Go ahead. And he shall send
his angel with the great sound of a
trumpet. And he shall send his angel
with the great sound of a trumpet. Go
ahead. And they shall gather together
HIS ELECT FROM THE FOUR winds from one
end of heaven to the other. Who is God's
elect? Israel.
That lets you know that we ain't going
back as a nation until Jesus return.
>> Right.
>> But he told you that
in Deuteronomy the 30th chapter and
ain't nobody listening. No, they ain't.
So until Jesus come, you going to be the
captain. But when that seventh trumpet
blows, sisters and brother,
that's when Jesus going to come. That's
when the dead and the first resurrection
is going to be raised.
And those of us that are going to be
living, that's going to make this thing,
we going to be changed. And that will
begin
Jesus thousand thousand-y year rule on
this earth. Let's go into second 1
Thessalonians the 4th chapter.
1 Thessalonians the 4th chapter and
we're going to start at verse 13. 1
Thessalonians 4 and13. Because sisters
and brothers, we serious here. And when
the Lord have us keep these feasts,
these are things that let you know why
the Lord have us keep these feasts. so
he can reveal all this to us.
And I'm going to pass it on. 1
Thessalonians 4 and 13. Go ahead and
read. But I would not have you to be
ignorant, brethren, concerning them
which are asleep.
>> Uh-huh.
>> That ye sorrow not even as others which
have no hope.
>> Go ahead.
>> For we believe that Jes, you know, I
wonder if I'll make it. Do you keep the
commandments? Yeah.
Then you going to make it. You don't
have to wonder about it. If you do the
right thing, you gonna make it.
>> Go ahead and read. For we believe that
Jesus died and rose again. And we do. Go
ahead. Even so them also which sleep in
Jesus will God bring with him.
>> Uh-huh. For this we say unto you by the
word of the Lord, that we which are
alive and remain until the coming of the
Lord should not prevent them which are
asleep. Now those of us see Jesus come
some people going to be living. We ain't
going to get in in the way of those that
are dead. Go ahead and read.
>> For the Lord himself shall descend from
heaven with a shout.
>> Uhhuh.
>> With the voice of the archangel.
>> Go ahead.
>> And with the trump of God.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And the dead in Christ shall rise first.
>> Go ahead.
>> Then we which are alive and remain shall
be caught up together with them in the
cloud to meet the Lord in the air. And
so shall we ever be with the Lord.
>> But the question that's begged to be
answered is where is that now?
Jesus done left heaven, right? And we
done left the earth and we have met
somewhere in between. This is what they
call the rapture, right?
>> But nobody bothers to notice that it
said that the Lord shall descend from
heaven,
>> right?
>> That mean he leaving heaven. When he
raised you, he ain't going to be there
no more,
>> right?
>> You going to meet him in there. So shall
we ever be with the Lord. Well, I'm
going to show you where. Let's go to
Zechariah the 14th chapter.
Zechariah chapter 14,
>> right? Go start reading at verse one.
We're gonna read verse one and then
we're gonna skip 14 and one. Read it.
Behold, the day of the Lord cometh and
thy spoil shall be devoured in the midst
of the
>> Uhhuh. Now skip down to verse three and
go ahead. Then shall the Lord go forth
and fight against those nations.
>> Go ahead.
>> As when he found the day of battle, and
his feet shall stand in that day upon
the Mount of Olives.
>> Wait a minute. and his feet going to
stand where?
>> That mount of olives.
>> That's on earth. Go ahead and read.
>> Which is before Jerusalem on the east.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the mount of olives shall cleave in
the midst thereof toward the east and
toward the west.
>> Go ahead.
>> And there shall be a very great valley.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And half of the mount shall remove
toward the north, and half of it toward
the south.
>> Go ahead.
>> And ye shall flee to the valley of the
mountains. For the valley of the
mountain shall reach into Ael.
>> Go ahead.
>> Yeah. Ye shall flee like as he fled FROM
BEFORE THE EARTHQUAKE IN THE day of
Ziah, king of Judah.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And the Lord my God shall come and all
the saints with thee.
>> Wait a minute. Where did he get them
saints from?
>> Met him in the air.
>> They met him in the air.
And when he get here,
what is he going to be ruler over? Skip
down and read verse nine.
Go ahead. And the Lord shall be king
over all the earth.
>> Uhhuh. In that day shall there be one
Lord and his name one. The Lord going to
be on this earth and he going to rule it
for a thousand years. And once it over
they going to turn over to the father.
But let's go to Leviticus the 25th
chapter and you got two more places
after this. I thought I'd give you some
hope.
Leviticus chapter 25.
This sums it up. Sisters and brothers,
rounds it off. 25 and1. Leviticus 25
and1.
Okay, read it. And the Lord spake unto
Moses of Mount Si, saying, speaking to
the children of Israel, saying unto
them, when you come into the land which
I give you, then shall the Lord keep a
Sabbath unto the Lord.
>> Uhhuh. Then shall you keep a Sabbath
unto the Lord. Six years thou shalt sew
thy field, and six years thou shalt
prune thy vineyard, and gather in the
fruit thereof.
>> So you're supposed to work the Lord for
six years, and on the seventh year, you
don't work the land rather, and you
don't work it then cuz you give your
land a Sabbath day rest. Go ahead and
read.
>> But in the seventh year, ye shall be a
Sabbath of rest unto the Lord, unto the
land.
>> Uhhuh.
>> A Sabbath for the Lord. Thou shalt
neither sow thy field nor prune thy
vineyard. Now skip down to verse eight
and continue.
And thou shall number seven Sabbath of
years unto thee, seven times seven
years, and the space of the seven
Sabbath of years shall be unto thee 49
years.
>> Uhhuh. Go ahead. Then thou shalt call
the trumpet of the Jews lead sound on
the 10th day of the seventh month. In
the day of atonement shall he make the
trumpet sound throughout all your land.
>> Now that's that's threatening to know
that this is what the coming of Jesus.
Jesus gonna come on the day of
atonement. That's when that trumpet
going to sound and everybody going to
have liberty throughout the land. But go
ahead and read what verse 10.
>> Go ahead.
>> And ye shall hollow the 50th year and
proclaim liberty throughout all the land
and to all the inhabitants thereof.
>> Go ahead.
>> It shall be a jubilee to you.
>> Uh-huh. [clears throat]
Now that 50th year is a jubilee, but
that 50th year represents the father's
kingdom, sisters and brothers.
Pentecost, this day represent the
father's kingdom because that is a day
after the Sabbath day.
>> Now Jesus ruled on this earth is going
to end
at the end of the s seventh day which is
the Sabbath.
And then he is going to turn it over to
the father. Let's go into first
Corinthians the 15th chapter.
>> You want to finish that?
>> What? What? What verse?
>> 10.
>> 10. Finish it. And it shall be a jubile
to you. Ye shall return every man into
his possession. Ye shall return every
man into his family.
>> And people don't understand that in the
father's kingdom, the Lord still going
to have the nations, but they all
[clears throat] going to be holy. They
all going to be immortal. and Jubilee
that mean that's going to be great
happenings ain't it?
>> Yes.
>> Cuz you done made the cut. You can
actually say I've been saved.
So at the end of that thousand years,
let's see what's going to happen. 1
Corinthians the 15th chapter.
1 Corinthians chapter 15.
Cuz I'm going to tell you something,
sisters and brother. There's some good
thing, good stuff in this book. All you
got to do is read it.
And when you read it, people want to
take issue with it.
Verse 21, 15 and verse 21.
Go ahead. For since by man came death,
by man came also the resurrection of the
dead.
>> Go ahead. For as in Adam all die, even
so in Christ shall all be made alive.
>> Go ahead.
>> Every man in his own order,
>> Uhhuh.
>> Christ the first fruits, afterward they
that are Christ at his coming.
>> Go ahead. Now let's that we read that
but then let's finish it. Go ahead.
>> Then cometh the end.
>> Uhhuh.
>> When he shall have delivered up the
kingdom to God
>> even the father
>> when he shall have put down all rule and
all authority and power.
>> But he must said then come at the end.
>> Yeah.
>> When he going to deliver the kingdom up
to the father. Jesus must put out all
rule all authority authority and all
enemies. Go ahead and read. For he must
reign till he have put all enemies under
his feet.
>> all enemies under his feet. Go ahead.
>> The last enemy that shall be destroyed
>> is death.
>> Now Jesus going to terminate death.
Ain't going to be no more dying.
None. Read verse 28 and go ahead. And
when all things shall be subdued unto
him, then shall the Son ALSO HIMSELF BE
SUBJECT unto him that put all things
under him, that God may be all in all.
Jesus will have finished his
job at the end of the thousand years
when the white throne judgments is over
with and death has been terminated.
Then here come New Jerusalem
on
Pentecost
of the 8th day
of the mara after the Sabbath day.
>> This is a great day here sister.
Now can't you see that 23rd chapter of
Leviticus is talking all talking about
spiritually coming of the Lord and
what's going to happen to us.
So before we go
it's something we always like to learn
like to read and because somewhere
somebody told somebody that smoking and
drinking especially drinking is sin.
Let's see what the Lord say about this
feast that we going that we having now.
Deuteronomy the 14th chapter. That's the
last one. Deuteronomy chapter 14.
We're going to start at verse 22.
Deuteronomy 14 and 22.
Okay. Go ahead. Thou shalt truly tide
all the increase of thy seed that the
field bringeth forth year by year. And
thou shalt eat before the Lord thy God,
in the place which he shall choose to
place his name there, the tide of thy
corn, of thy wine, of the and of the
tide of thine oil, and the first of the
herd, and of thy flocks, that thou
mayest learn to fear the Lord thy God
always. Go ahead. And if the way be too
long for thee, so that thou art not able
to carry it, or if the place be too far
for thee, which the Lord thy God shall
choose to set his name there.
>> Uhhuh.
>> For the Lord thy God have blessed thee,
then shall thou turn it into money, and
bind up the money in thine hand, and
shall go into the place which the Lord
thy God shall choose. Now once the Lord
say look you you take who whoever you
bringing cow you bringing a cab you
bringing wine or whatever the Lord said
bring it to the place where he used but
if the place be too far from you you
know to drive your cows to look whatever
you going then sell it and get the money
and do what with it
up read it keep reading and thou shalt
bestow that money for whatsoever thy
soul lustth after. Go ahead for oxen.
for auction or for sheep
>> for sheep
>> or for wine
>> or for strong drink
>> or for jack Daniel
>> and do what? Go ahead.
>> Or for whatsoever thy soul desireth, and
thou shalt eat there before the Lord thy
God, and thou shalt rejoice thou and
thine household. So this what we going
to do. We going to eat this food, drink
a little wine, come over with some Jack
Daniel. I'm gonna have you squirted off
the lot.
We ain't having it here.